educationgrant.com 2017-09-11

# EducationGrant - Avenue100 Media Solutions

EducationGrant.com PRIVACY POLICY (this “Policy”) Effective Date: December 3, 2008

This privacy statement covers the web site www.EducationGrant.com (the “Site”) and is applicable to all information about you (“you”) collected through the Site.

EducationGrant.com (“EducationGrant”, “we,” “us,” or “our”) discloses the information collection and usage practices applicable to the Site in this Policy. This Policy describes the types of information that EducationGrant gathers from you and the other people who visit the Site (the “Users”) and how we may use that information. By providing any information, you agree to our use of that information consistent with this Policy. This Privacy Policy may change from time to time as our business model changes. You should check for changes on the Site whenever you visit.

EducationGrant collects personally identifiable information from our Users at several different points on our Site.

Please read this Policy carefully before providing us with any information. If you have questions about this Policy, e-mail us at info@EducationGrant.com.

##### Registration

Users are welcome to browse our Site; however, in order to participate in some of our services. Users may be required to complete brief registration forms which may or may not ask for personally identifiable information. When personally identifiable information is collected, it is subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

##### Personally Identifiable Information

All Users have the option of providing various types of personally identifiable information to us through the Site. For example, you may choose to provide us your name, mailing address, telephone number, or e-mail address or other personally identifiable information. We collect this personally identifiable information when you, at any point, manually enter it into any online form available on the Site. We may also store your personally identifiable information in our systems for use in other ways as described in this Policy.

In order for you to take full advantage of the Site, we encourage you to provide your personally identifiable information to us. Providing your personally identifiable information is, however, voluntary. You may choose not to provide us with your personally identifiable information by simply not entering it on the Site. While you still will have access to the Site even if you do not provide us with your personally identifiable information, you should understand that you will not be able to use certain of the services or features available through the Site that require you to enter your personally identifiable information in order to function.

If you do not input any of your personally identifiable information, then the information we collect from you is limited. For example, we log your IP address in order to help us to diagnose problems with our server, administer the Site and track usage statistics. Your IP address may vary each time you visit, or it may be the same, depending on whether you access the Site through an always-on type of Internet connection (such as cable or DSL), or through a dial-up connection. Either way, it would be very difficult for us to personally identify you through your IP address. We match IP addresses to completed User registration forms for validation and error checking purposes. If you reached the Site by clicking on a link or ad from another site, then we may also log that information. This helps us to maximize our Internet exposure and to understand the interests of our Users. In general, this information is used to generate overall anonymous reports on our Users that enable us to improve the effectiveness of the Site.

##### Cookies

We often place a small file known as a “cookie” on your computer’s hard drive. A cookie may contain information that allows us to track your path through the Site and to determine whether you have visited us before. However, unless you provide us with personally identifiable information, the cookies will not contain any information that would allow us to personally identify you. If you do provide personally identifiable information to us, the cookie is tied to this information so that our systems will recognize you each time you visit the Site. In that way, we can save your preferences from visit to visit and present you with a customized version of the Site, without requiring you to log into the Site every time you visit. Our cookies cannot be used to read data from your hard drive and cannot retrieve information from any other cookies created by other sites. We use cookies in this manner to help us understand how Users use the Site, and to help us to improve the Site. You may refuse to accept a cookie from us by following the procedures for rejecting cookies specific to your web browser. Although you may do so, you may find that your browser reacts strangely when visiting not only the Site, but other web sites as well.

If you visit the web site of one of our business partners (e.g., advertisers) by clicking on a link for this Site, they may also use cookies on their web site. We have no access to or control over these cookies. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by EducationGrant.com only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

##### User Activity Tracking

We employ software technology that enables us to track certain aspects of a User’s visit to the Site. This technology helps us better manage content on the Site by informing us what content is effective. The software uses two methods to track User activity: 1) “trackers” and 2) “clear gifs”. Trackers are pieces of executable code that are embedded in a web page that track usage activity including which pages are viewed, when they are viewed, and how long the pages are viewed. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with unique identifiers that are embedded in web pages and e-mails that track whether or not a User has viewed a particular page or e-mail. User activity information may be associated with additional information about a User’s session, such as IP Address and the type of browser used, and personally identifiable information, if provided by the User.

If you arrive at the Site by “clicking through” from another web site, and you have registered with that other web site, then certain information about you that you provided to that other web site, such as the terms you were searching on that led you to the Site, may be transmitted to us and we may use it. You should review the privacy policy of any web site from which you reached the Site in order to determine what information was collected by that web site and for what purpose(s) you agreed that web site could use that information. We may or may not retain that information; if we do, then we will only use it in accordance with this Policy. This information may or may not be associated with other User activity data or personally identifiable information.

##### EducationGrant’s Policy Regarding Children Under the Age of 13

The Site is not intended for children under the age of 13, and EducationGrant does not knowingly collect or use personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13

##### How We Use the Information We Collect

We may use the information (whether or not personally identifiable) that you provide to us to, among other things:

  * Make your next visit to the Site more personalized.
  * Process or complete transactions requested by you.
  * Email information and offers to you.
  * Mail information and offers to you.
  * Make telephone calls to you with information and offers.
  * Provide your information to trusted business partners to fulfill services you have requested.
  * Compile anonymous statistical information and analysis. 
  * Contact you regarding administrative issues such as questions about your specific request
  * Provide compiled anonymous information to third parties.
  * Provide, sell, or rent your information to third parties for advertising purposes.

##### Consent to the Use of Third Party Providers 

Please understand that EducationGrant may contract with third parties to provide various services to EducationGrant relating to the Site on an outsourced basis rather than performing the services itself. For example, we may contract with an e-mail provider to handle the distribution of e-mail messages to Users of the Site. Likewise, we may contract with a web site hosting provider to host the Site for us. We may also contract with various validation services to confirm contact information you provide. By visiting the Site, all Users consent to EducationGrant providing all information (whether or not personally identifiable) received or collected from those Users to such third party providers for the purpose of enabling the third party provider to provide these outsourced services to us. In addition, all Users consent to the collection, maintenance, and processing of their information (whether or not personally identifiable) by EducationGrant and these third party providers.

We will share information provided by Users (whether or not personally identifiable) with certain trusted business partners in our network so that they can contact you with information about the services in which you have expressed interest or a broader range of services and information that we believe will meet your needs. In order to provide the services available to you on this Site, we may also supplement your information (whether or not personally identifiable) with information from third party sources with whom we have contracted for the purpose of verifying the contact information you have provided. You have the option not to have your information shared with business partners by not requesting these services or by e-mailing info@EducationGrant.com or by phone at the number below.

##### Opting Out 

This privacy statement describes EducationGrant’s uses of your information. If you do not agree to our uses of your personally identifiable information as we have described for you, you are not required to provide that information to us. In addition, if we send e-mails to you, you may opt out of receiving non-administrative e-mails from us simply by responding to the opt-out link provided on all e-mail communications from EducationGrant.

##### Communications From Us

We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account. We will contact you either through e-mail, telephone, or postal mail.

When it is necessary to do so, we will send you service-related announcements, primarily via e-mail. For example, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we may send you an e-mail. Generally, you may not opt out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account by calling the phone number listed at the end of this Policy.

##### Surveys & Contests

From time-to-time our Site will request personally identifiable information from Users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the User therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose personally identifiable information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code). Contact information will be shared with the contest or survey sponsors to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of the Site. Users’ personally identifiable information collected through surveys or contests is not shared with third parties who are not agents, service providers or business partners, unless we give prior notice and receive your permission for the sharing. Though we may use an intermediary to conduct these surveys or contests, these intermediaries will not use the Users’ personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.

##### Other Web Sites; Links

Please be aware that EducationGrant’s affiliated institutions, promotional partners, advertisers, sponsors, and other third-party web sites accessible through the Site may have their own privacy and data collection policies and practices. If you leave our Site through a link to a third party website, EducationGrant is not responsible for any actions, content of web sites or privacy policies of such third parties. You should check the applicable privacy policies of those third parties when providing information through linked web sites.

##### Disclosure of Your Information

EducationGrant in some circumstances may be legally required to disclose information (including personally identifiable information) in response to requests from law enforcement authorities, or in response to a subpoena or other legal process. If that happens, we will provide only the information required. We can also turn over information about you if we believe we must in order to prevent a violation of the law, and by accepting this Policy, you consent to our right to do so, in our sole discretion. You also consent to our disclosing information about you in the course of legal proceedings if we believe we are legally required to do so, if we reasonably believe that doing so may mitigate our liability, or if doing so will assist us in enforcing our legal rights.

At some point, EducationGrant may establish subsidiaries or other related companies, or merge with or be acquired by another company. When that happens, then we may disclose to them your personally identifiable information, in which case we will request them to abide by this Policy. We may also disclose some personally identifiable information to a potential acquirer, although such disclosure would generally be subject to confidentiality requirements.

We reserve the right to modify this Policy at any time, so please review the Site frequently for any changes. Amendments to this Policy will be posted on the Site and will be effective when posted. You will be deemed to have been made aware of, will be subject to, and will be deemed to have accepted, the changes to any amended or revised Policy by your continued use of our services or the Site.

Of course, EducationGrant will take reasonable measures to secure the personally identifiable information Users provide to us, using industry-standard methods. All personally identifiable information is protected by password and accessible only to authorized EducationGrant personnel. However, there is a remote possibility that Internet transmissions containing a User’s personally identifiable information may be intercepted by others. There is no way for us to ensure the privacy of User information before it arrives at the Site or after it leaves the Site.

Avenue100 Media Solutions owns and operates www.educationgrant.com
